findingsingles.net 2010-06-11

# FindingSingles.net

## Privacy Policy

FindingSingles.net is in partnership with Singlesnet.com. FindingSingles.net captures and passes your information on to the Singlesnet.com system. In order to complete this transaction, FindingSingles.net requires that you provide your e-mail address, zip code, age and gender. We also collect your IP address and related information from your browser, and we use cookies to remember your computer when you return to the site. 

If you choose to upgrade your Singlesnet.com membership for a fee, we require your name, credit card information and billing address in order to process the transaction. No other personally identifiable information is required for the site, although your personal profile may include additional information about yourself, including photographs. 

All personally identifiable information collected by FindingSingles.net is only used in connection with the services offered at Singlesnet.com. As a part of our service we sometimes post and feature photographs provided by our members in print and online, accompanied by the member's profile. Singlesnet.com does not share your personally identifiable information with any unaffiliated third parties for marketing purposes. We may share your information with our affiliates, which are companies controlled by, controlling or under common control with Singlesnet.com. 

We may engage unaffiliated third parties to assist with services related to the website, including but not limited to hosting, marketing and promotional activities, technical support and credit card processing services. These third parties are obligated to keep the information secure and confidential and must use the information only in connection with providing services to Singlesnet.com. 

Singlesnet.com may, from time to time, communicate with you regarding customer service or to inform you of special offers that we believe you may be interested in. At that time we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out and not to receive further information about that special offer, or other similar offers. To opt-out of any or all of our email notifications, click "My account" and un-check the unwanted items from the section named "Email settings". 

The information collected by Singlesnet.com may be transferred in connection with the sale or merger of the company, or a sale of substantially all the assets, or in connection with a bankruptcy. We may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with court orders or with requests by law enforcement agencies, to enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect the rights, property, safety of our website and other users of the site. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 09/04/2008. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect on this site. 

If you have any questions about this statement, please contact us via the contact form or direct your mail to: 

**FindingSingles.net**   
185 - 911 Yates Street   
Ste 304   
Victoria, BC   
V8V 4Y9   
info@findingsingles.net
